The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The Southern Domain of Allheaven
is a wasteland.
Most planets here are abandoned
with very little spiritual energy.
That's why strong cultivators aren't willing to set foot here.
Instead, it has become a sanctuary for mortals
and low-level cultivation families.
Perfect.
This place is secluded enough.
I still have 20 years before
the Thunder Celestial Realm opens.
During this time, I have 2 important things to do.
The first one
is to adjust my spells
that don't align with the third step I saw.
That way, I won't walk the wrong path.
The second one
is to gather resentment
for the Underworld River.
Damn sword intent,
Grandpa Xu has finally conquered you !
From now on,
I am the true Sword Spirit !
Little Lin,
are you still not letting me out ?
Noisy...
Just you wait...
We're not done yet !
The aura of this planet
Planet Qing Lin\NSouthern Domain\NAllheaven Star System
is similar to Planet Suzaku.
This planet has many mortals
and its strongest cultivator is only Nascent Soul.
There's not a single Soul Formation cultivator.
Many cultivation families depend on mortal kingdoms to survive.
Because the spiritual energy is scarce,
it's difficult for them to grow.
This is exactly what I need.
Father,
slow down.
Zhang Yang\NYoung Master of the Zhang Family\NEarly stage Nascent Soul
Zhang Xinhai\NZhang Family Head\NLate stage Nascent Soul
Your father
has little time left.
The Zhang Family Head of every generation
must personally set foot on this peak
to gaze upon the heavens and the earth
and try to understand them.
This is the ancestral rule.
Looking back, I, Zhang Xinhai,
have led the Zhang Family for centuries.
The Zhang Family
has become the number one family on this planet.
The previous Zhang Family Heads were also diligent
so why
don't the heavens let us live longer ?
In the end,
I was stuck at Late stage Nascent Soul
unable to reach Soul Formation.
What a pity...
Father...
This person...
I wasn't able to see him
when I used my Divine Sense earlier
but I can clearly see him with my eyes.
What level of cultivation is this ?
This place
is not bad.
What a pity
that such a peak
is being used by you guys as a graveyard.
Junior Zhang Xinhai pays respects to Senior.
If Senior likes this Heng Yun Peak,
Junior will offer it to you immediately.
Your lifespan is nearly exhausted.
Even with my power,
it's hard to solve.
Senior misunderstood me.
Junior understands the will of the heavens.
Before I die,
I would like to have the tremendous opportunity
to witness Senior's spells.
That way, I'll die without regrets.
Not to mention this peak,
I'll even gift you
Planet Qing Lin
if Senior likes it.
I can't defy the heavens
to change your fate.
But I can ignite your remaining spiritual energy
to extend your lifespan
by 10 years.
I can barely perform this spell
after seeing the third step.
If I had known this option existed back then,
Wan'er wouldn't be like this...
Thank you, Senior, for giving me a second life.
Thank you, Senior !
Senior, what are your instructions ?
The entire Zhang Family
will do its best
to carry them out.
I give you 10 years
to gather
as much resentment from mortals as possible.
The more the better.
If I’m pleased with your result,
then
as long as I'm on this planet,
your Zhang Family
will never lose its legacy.
Father,
who is this person ?
Don't ask too much !
Quick,
let's return to the family.
Mobilize the whole family
no matter the cost
to work for Senior.
This is the Zhang Family's
heaven-sent fortune !
From today onward,
this planet
belongs to me.
The area 10 000 li from Heng Yun Peak
is now a restricted area.
Intruders
will not be shown mercy.
On this day,
I became the ruler of Planet Qing Ling.
The restricted area of Heng Yun:
10 000 li sealed off.
The Soul Lasher...
I have many artifacts.
In terms of offense,
the celestial sword and the half-moon blade are stronger.
In terms of defense,
the Billion-Soul Flag and the Mountains and Rivers Painting are sturdier.
In terms of abilities,
the Celestial Mountain and the God Slaying Chariot are more versatile.
But this whip
is the only one that faintly touches upon the third step I glimpsed at.
It subtly aligns with the meaning of karma.
My domain
has gradually shifted from Life and Death toward Karma.
But this path is vast
and with my current comprehension
I'm not yet able to materialize it.
I can probably use this whip to carry my domain
and slowly materialize it.
Merging my domain and an artifact...
The Dao is within oneself.
I'll use this whip as a proxy,
to temporarily carry karma.
I hope
it will not betray my Dao.
5 years later
Zhang Family Residence\NPlanet Qing Lin
Family Head,
70% of the resentment from the West Mountains Region has been gathered.
But the land is vast
and mortals are scattered.
It will be difficult to accelerate.
The situation on the eastern sea islands is even worse.
Although there are numerous islanders,
travel time is the issue.
Flying all over the place
takes a lot of time.
Faster !
You must do it faster !
Half of the 10 years deadline has passed
and we have gathered less than 40%.
Senior's order
will determine the future of our Zhang Family !
Issue the order,
all family members
must spare no cost
and work day and night
in order to complete Senior's order !
Understood !
A dead end ?
Nothing but dead ends !
We
have stumbled into the Heng Yun restricted area.
Don't...
Don't scare yourself.
Maybe...
it's just some mountain fog.
You don't know how
the Nascent Soul Ancestors from the Li Family of West City
met their end ?
Where did this outsider come from ?
Who dares to claim Planet Qing Lin ?
Break for me !
Even Nascent Soul Ancestors
were crushed like bugs.
And we, two mortals,
won't even fill the gaps in those ghost's teeths...
Ancestor, spare us !
We didn't mean to intrude.
We...
are not dead ?
Thank you, Ancestor, for sparing our lives !
Thank you for your mercy, Ancestor !
Ancestor is kind !
After 5 years of refining,
the domain started merging.
Using this whip to wield karma
Karma Whip
is more convenient
than using Divine Sense to control my domain.
It should be twice as strong now.
However,
I still need to test it.
Little Lin,
stop fiddling with that little broken whip.
Your Grandpa Xu
now carries ancient sword intent.
Come out.
You still dare speak to Grandpa Xu like that ?
Little Lin,
you still haven't grasped the situation.
I'm not the same Xu Liguo from back then anymore !
What the hell is this thing !?
Every being in this world
is subject to karma.
There is no place
without karmic causes.
And karmic effects
are everywhere.
The karmic effect is also the source of the karmic cause.
Master, have mercy !
I'm dissipating !
I'm really
going to dissipate !
You obtained your ancient sword intent
thanks to me.
The resulting karmic effect
belongs to me as well.
Little Xu knows he was wrong !
I was truly wrong...
Besides,
if it weren't for Master
refining me into a devil back then,
how could I be where I am today ?
No, no, no...
I meant...
How could I have the fortune to stay by Master's side ?
That is your karma,
not mine.
Xu Liguo, you idiot !
Why do you always forget
that the fiend is more of a devil than me...
Master !
Master, have mercy !
Little Xu knows he was wrong !
I'm really sorry !
This is not a joke !
It's decently strong.
Master's skills are unparalleled !
Just now,
Little Xu was just putting on an act
all so Master could test his spells some more.
Little Xu is loyal to you.
The heavens are my witness !
I’m completely devoted to you.
Since you're out now,
you can stay outside for a bit.
Use the 10 000 li around this peak
to comprehend your sword intent on your own.
Freedom...?
Wait...No...
There must be a trap.
This is a test.
It must be a test !
Master...
Xu Liguo can't bear to leave you !
Only by your side
does Little Xu feel at ease !
As you wish.
I knew it was a test.
Trying to outsmart me ?
Whoever causes trouble
will be confined for a century.
Master sure has a way with beasts.
The time I spend on Planet Qing Ling
is one of the rare moments of peace
in my cultivation journey.
The 10 years deadline
is coming soon.
Give this pill to him.
If he is talented enough,
he may have a chance
to reach Soul Formation.
Thank you, Senior !
As the next Family Head, Zhang Yang,
took his father's place in serving me.
By my order,
he began planting Celestial Ascension Fruits
on planet Qing Lin.
And after the Underworld River absorbed the resentment,
the river's soul started taking shape.
Despite my efforts,
I haven't made progress in refining my spells.
It's a process of trial and error.
By contemplating the direction of the third step,
my domain
unknowingly
reached the absolute peak of Ascendant.
20 months after the Life and Death Domain was completed,
my cultivation
also reached Peak Late stage Ascendant.
Wang Lin's avatar\NPeak Late stage Ascendant
1000 years of cultivation
to complete the first step.
Even Zhuque Zi, who I once had to look up to,
is already behind me.
On this path of cultivation,
I've finally reached the end of the first step.
Before the Thunder Celestial Realm opens,
I still have
3 months.
half a month later
The Thunder Celestial Realm
requires a Thunder Cauldron to enter.
If I find Shengong Hu, he may give me a cauldron.
But that means he'll see how strong I am.
It's too risky.
According to Shengong Hu,
the Thunder Celestial Temple distributes the Thunder Cauldrons
based on the strength of each cultivation family.
About now,
should be the time when they retrieve their Thunder Cauldrons.
Planet Sheng Tan\NSouthern Domain\NAllheaven Star System
Welcome, Lord Messenger.
Zhang Zhen\NZhang Family Ancestor\NIllusory Yin
Our Sheng Tan Planet is blessed with your presence.
We appreciate your guidance.
An Illusory Yin cultivator ?
It seems Shengong Hu's intelligence was outdated.
Are you
returning with the Thunder Cauldrons ?
That's right.
If Lord Messenger has any instructions,
please speak freely.
I need a Thunder Cauldron.
This old man has just been to the Thunder Celestial Temple
where I heard a rumor about a madman
who dared to impersonate a messenger.
I thought it was just some nonsense.
But after seeing you today,
I'm convinced.
You
are the impostor !
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Ask
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Can the mundane world be shattered
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles
as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what
my journey to treading the heavens relies on.